<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jordan Lowes</title>
    <description>A Personal blog site/portfolio
</description>
    <link>http://jordann.github.io//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jordann.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 12:07:09 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 12:07:09 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Matters Of Moments</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;MOM stands for &amp;quot;matter of moments&amp;quot;. In short it is a time tracking tool which understands that you don&amp;#39;t want 
to have to think about how to record your time, instead you want it to seize the moments of attention that you award it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MOM is all about building operational software in new and sane way that will ready us for the growth of the application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal is to create an application that is completely Decentralized. Seperating all our concerns creates 
an application that can grow well in the open source community. By using tools that can help us enforce this 
practice we hope to get a better understanding on creating apps that are very clear and readable by someone looking to contribute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the development I find that I am always learning new things and how to incorporate different frameworks and packages
into the work flow. Hopefully the app will be done soon to show off and get more people involved in the process!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 07:14:25 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://jordann.github.io//mobile/application/2014/11/03/mom-app.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jordann.github.io//mobile/application/2014/11/03/mom-app.html</guid>
        
        <category>regular</category>
        
        
        <category>mobile</category>
        
        <category>application</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Just started this site to be used as a blog/portfolio web site. I decided to go with a static site generator of Jekyll.
This lets me use Markdown which is great. This makes adding posts and editing them very easy. Since im using github to version control 
my site I can easily add a blog post from any device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m going to be adding to the design and updating the site throughout the next weeks, if you are interested about creating a static site 
and having it GitHub serve it up, I added a couple links below for you to get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll-help&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s dedicated Help repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn how to serve it up with &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 10:34:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://jordann.github.io//jekyll/update/2014/10/29/welcome-to-jekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jordann.github.io//jekyll/update/2014/10/29/welcome-to-jekyll.html</guid>
        
        <category>featured</category>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
